You're watching Chef & My Fridge
with very special guests.
Can you see
that we have a few more chairs today?
-Let's welcome the special guests.
-Who could it be?
Please welcome today's fridge owners.
Come on out!
Today's fridge owners.
Looking cool!
The sisters, BIBI and NaKyoung,
and the siblings, Jonathan and Patricia.
-Hello.
WELCOME
Welcome.
-Hello.
-This way.
Hold my hand.
LEAVES
-You have to hold my hand.
-I have to?
-You should hold her hand.
-Check on your sister.
-Goodness.
-No way.
SQUEAL
We've put together…
-How special.
-…a siblings special.
Allow me to introduce them.
Please welcome BIBI
and NaKyoung of tripleS.
Welcome.
WELCOMING WILDLY
Hello.
I am… Um…
I sing and act,
and I'm Kim Hyeong-seo…
I mean, BIBI.
She must be really nervous.
You're Kim Hyeong-seo when you act,
and BIBI when you sing.
BIBI Kim Hyeong-seo.
Hello, I'm a member of tripleS,
and the most charming one of the 24,
NaKyoung.
Yes, she's right.
Among 24 members.
-Let's go over to that side.
-Yes, these siblings.
Spicy, oh so spicy
-Their diss battle…
-Sorry?
-"Spicy."
-It's different for us.
The comical siblings' diss battle
took over the TV show industry.
Please welcome Jonathan and Patricia.
Welcome.
-All right.
-Woo-hoo!
-Hi…
-Hello, all the way from Jeolla-do,
-…I'm Jonathan.
-And I'm Patricia.
Hello.
HOW ADORABLE
All the way from Jeolla-do?
HOMEY DIALECT
Where are you two from?
We were born
in the Democratic Republic of the Congo.
I moved to Korea when I was eight,
then went to Jeolla-do in "sigth" grade.
-"Sigth."
THE ORIGINAL JEOLLA-DO DIALECT
-So we're from Gwangju.
-Gwangju.
BIBI and NaKyoung, where are you two from?
Born in Busan, raised in Ulsan,
then went to school in Changwon.
We pretty much kept to Gyeongsang-do.
This is our Hwagae Market special.
We're in for a lot of fun today.
BIBI claimed
to have grown up with Chef & My Fridge.
So you've been a fan since you were 15?
I've watched it since the first episode.
-Really?
-Back in 2014?
Yes, when you launched the show.
-Are you serious?
-Yes.
Internet TV was a thing,
so I'd buy the show
-for 1,190 won per episode.
-You remember that?
-You paid for the show? 1,190 won?
-I did.
-Yes.
-She did that? She's a real fan.
-I really loved it.
-She watched it so often.
That's why I'm so nervous right now.
We took a few years off
before returning, right?
-By then, I was already someone on TV.
-Yes, you had debuted.
I told myself, "I'll be on the show."
"I'll be on the show!"
HER BUCKET LIST
You'll somehow be on the show.
"I'll somehow get myself on it."
And I'm here!
SQUEAL
She's on the show.
She grew up with the show,
and now she's on it.
Did you watch the show with BIBI?
I did.
She always had dibs
on the remote control, so…
THE REMOTE CONTROL BELONGS TO THE ELDEST
The hierarchy seems
quite established with that family.
What about you?
We had to work for it. For example…
When our teachers ended the day
with the homeroom meeting,
I'd sit like this
and shoot out as soon as we were done.
DASHING BACK HOME
Whoever gets the remote control is it.
Whoever gets it.
-Grab it first to win.
So you take it with you
even to the bathroom.
NEVER LET YOUR GUARD DOWN
It doesn't matter where I go.
I have to take it with me
no matter where I go.
AMAZED…
But you never took it by force.
-We never did that.
-We didn't do that.
We heard from a tipster that Patricia
has been envious of NaKyoung.
You're right.
I've always wanted
an older sister since I was young.
I also saw them on Men on a Mission,
and the way BIBI looked at her
seemed so loving, so I was jealous.
That's far from the truth.
THE LOOK THAT PATRICIA SAW
The look in her eyes
was definitely different.
Also, there are so many things
that sisters can share with one another,
-such as clothes and makeup.
-That's true.
So what's it like, NaKyoung?
-I can always borrow her clothes.
-Right? And makeup.
And there are things
that sisters can talk about.
It can be fun for you.
Do you want to try it for a month?
You're handing her over?
It's like you want to get rid of me.
"Do you want to try it for a month?"
EVEN JEALOUS OF THEM BICKERING♥
I'm sure BIBI has made you feel
wronged and frustrated before.
I've been a victim
of her gaslighting quite a lot,
-especially with food.
-Food?
-Me too.
-Especially so
because she's really into food.
I'm a bit of a glutton.
-There was a candy called Jjakggung.
-I know that.
GRAPE & STRAWBERRY FLAVORED
Everyone knows that
-the grape flavor is much better.
-It's absolutely better.
But she'd say,
"Strawberry flavor is much better."
I'd go, "Look, it's pink."
"It's such a pretty pink."
Why do I feel so guilty?
(HAS A SISTER)
So one day…
HER GASLIGHTING DAYS…
She'd usually eat it, though annoyed,
but that day, she said,
"You eat it all, pig!"
-She blew up. She threw it out there.
-She has had enough.
She's not going to put up with it anymore.
-Can't do that with food.
-It's…
She won't take it every time.
STILL, I WISH I HAD A SISTER♥
Here's something Jonathan said.
"Even if Patricia had an older sister,
she would've been beaten a lot."
That's right.
-That's too harsh.
-Why did you say that?
-She's the type who asks for trouble.
-She asks for trouble?
No way.
When she's not happy with something.
-she immediately stops calling me oppa.
-That's not it.
-She goes, "Hey," or "Jonathan."
-Wait, no.
Do you do that?
-I wouldn't call her "hey."
-She wouldn't.
I don't say that.
Then what, in English?
-I'd go, "Nathan."
-"Nathan."
I say it all cute. "Nathan."
Do you think she asks for trouble?
Very often.
When I was young,
-he once punched me with his fist.
-My gosh.
You'll see that my face is asymmetrical.
A SPICY EXPOSÉ
CHUCKLING…
My left side
looks different from the right.
-You.
-I can see it.
-You're dying to get TV gigs.
-He punched me like this.
-Like this.
-Wait a second.
Jonathan, let us hear her out first.
-He has always loved milk tea.
-Milk tea.
HEADACHE
One day, he made a pretty big batch,
so I asked him for a sip,
but he wouldn't give it to me.
I was young and quite mad,
so I went behind his back
and spit into it.
WHAT?
-Into his tea?
-You spit into it?
I spit into it,
and I guess he must've seen me do it.
NODDING
"You're going to get punched, you know."
When he said that, I went…
BLEHHHHH
TEASING WITH ALL HER MIGHT
-That was all I could do.
-That's annoying.
He warned me three times,
then I blacked out.
He had punched me.
WHOOSH…
I had a huge pride, so I said,
"It didn't even hurt."
Then I cried in exactly three seconds.
"It didn't even hurt…" Then I bawled.
When she said it didn't hurt,
I was getting ready to punch her again.
She said it didn't hurt,
so I was getting myself ready.
I was like this,
but thankfully, she cried.
WHAT A RELIEF
-I shouldn't have done that. Drink this.
-"Drink this."
-Thanks.
-They're funny.
-He opened it for you.
What's this about you two wrestling often?
Patricia claims that
she's been the only one who got abused,
but it went both ways.
There's something called WWE,
and I'm a huge fan.
I CAN SEE WHAT'S COMING…
-So I'd lay out a futon…
-Right.
With his younger sister?
-…and wrestle with her.
-Really?
And it was a fair fight?
-So fair.
-Totally.
We were on par with each other.
-An equal fight.
-Yes.
-We were in elementary school.
-Back in elementary school.
-In elementary school.
-It was an equal fight?
I'd be lying there,
telling Patricia to jump from the sofa.
-Slam!
-Just like that.
At times, she'd do this with her elbow.
We put out the futon and did that
at least three times a week.
But it wasn't a real fight.
-It wasn't a real fight.
-No.
Just like them,
our fight also wasn't one-sided.
It was a one-on-one fight.
-It was a one-on-one fight?
-It was.
Out of ten fights,
she'd win at least four.
THEY'RE NECK-AND-NECK TOO
She has that grit.
GOT GRIT
-How do sisters fight?
-Was she good?
GRABS
SQUEAL
A TUG-OF-WAR?
Do you pull out each other's hair?
-We have rules too.
-You had rules?
It's something like this.
BUILDING TENSION
So whoever is pushed back loses?
Something like that.
It's just like
how a wrestling match starts.
-It's like that.
-It's similar.
It's similar.
Eun-yeong, you have a twin sister, right?
We were the double high beams
of Geumjeong-dong.
-We were famous.
-The dazzling sisters.
I think our fights were pretty intense.
We often made use of objects. For example,
-we'd throw a fan at each other.
-A fan?
-When we did that,
-…the neck of the fan got bent.
-Right.
Our parents told us
to keep using the same fan
because we did that in a fight,
so we literally used this broken
and shaky fan for five years.
What are you saying?
-Shaky?
-Yes, also,
-…do you remember D's juice bottle?
-Yes, that one is really sturdy.
I once threw that at my sister.
-But that woman dodged it right away.
-"That woman"?
It's like a scene from Rustic Period.
-She dodged it.
-She went for her sister.
BRUTAL
So our fights were pretty intense.
See? I'm much better.
NOT TRUE
ONLY THE STRONGEST SURVIVED
IN GEUMJEONG-DONG
You may fight from time to time,
-but you probably make up with each other.
-That's important.
In our case,
I always initiate it.
-You request it first?
-I knew it. It's the older sister.
"I'm getting tteokbokki.
Are you going to eat some?"
I know what that is. That's so accurate.
I KNOW WHAT THAT IS
I know that vibe.
"I'm making ramyeon. Do you want some?"
THE SISTERS' CUTE FORMULA TO MAKE PEACE
-That's cute.
-One time at an awards ceremony,
NaKyoung did a kissing performance
-out in the open for everyone to see.
-You kissed her?
-We were both doing well in that season,
-Why?
…so we saw each other
all the time at ceremonies.
-I see.
-One day,
we ran into each other at the venue,
and she said,
"I'll kiss you if you win an award today."
OH MY
I thought, "Sure, great for me."
Looking back, I think
she took advantage of me.
How did she do that?
It went viral immediately.
-She had a plan.
-Just like Sung-jun.
She's good.
Honestly, she may have
taken advantage of me,
but I was still proud.
"She has become someone
who knows how to get things her way."
"My sister is a big girl now."
She is.
What were you really thinking?
-She's precisely right.
-Precisely right?
SHE MADE PRECISE USE OF HER SISTER
-Precisely right? She's good.
-It's like this.
I had an ambitious plan.
Also, she likes it when I kiss her.
She likes it.
Our family tends to be
very physically affectionate.
Light kisses happen all the time.
UNIMAGINABLE…
Kisses on the cheek happen daily.
-I can do it now.
-You can?
WHOA!
QUITE SHOCKED
THE SIBLINGS HAVE NEVER SEEN THIS HAPPEN
At an awards ceremony,
he practically pushed me over.
I fell at an awards show.
Now that I heard that story,
I realize they were kissing there
while he was knocking me over.
He got embarrassed about me.
Can you two do it too?
That's the worst. I can't do that to him.
SHE'S ABOUT TO GET FURIOUS
But you're family.
-Because we're family.
-Because you're family?
That doesn't happen between siblings.
How loving can you be?
-Sitting next to each other.
-Yes.
Sharing the same air in the same space.
THE MOST THEY CAN DO IS SHARE AIR
Or how you end up
rubbing on each other when you fight.
-Rubbing skin.
-Yes.
-I'd throw her, and when she returns,
-Yes, throwing.
-…I'd pin her down.
-That's it.
-Wrestling.
-That's all.
THE SIBLINGS' TAKE: WRESTLING IS LOVING
Right now, we're the most physical
we have ever been.
-This doesn't happen often.
-I see.
-Sitting next to each other?
-We're dead serious.
Just sharing the same air.
What if you go really viral
for kissing his cheek?
-No, thanks.
-It'll literally give us viruses.
THE VIRAL SIBLINGS
Getting sick.
We once had to hold hands
while shooting an ad.
It must've been so hard.
-We had to hold it for a while.
-Right.
-They kept insisting.
-You'd do it for money?
-Yes.
-We can do that.
They'd do it for money.
-They'll need cash.
-Yes, right.
It's in the contract.
Hug, plus so-and-so won.
EXTRA CHARGES FOR PHYSICAL TOUCH:
HOLD HANDS, HUG, KISS
The rate also goes by the minute.
-So the rate changes?
-It does.
STRATEGIC WITH NUMBERS
-So you two can touch for money.
-Yes.
-We're business-oriented.
-Exclusively business-oriented.
-They're true siblings.
-They are.
We're now about to go through
the Gyeongsang-do sisters,
BIBI and NaKyoung's fridge.
Do you two use this together?
The fridge itself is mine.
But we often make something
whenever she comes over.
Yes, I go over often,
-so you'll see some traces of mine.
-I see.
I starved myself yesterday.
-Because we took your fridge.
-Because of that.
Right. We take everything.
-We present BIBI and NaKyoung's fridge!
-Fridge!
THEY HAVE LOTS OF STUFF!
PRESENTING BIBI & KIM NAKYOUNG'S FRIDGE
THE FRIDGE IS LOADED
Your fridge is full.
-Whoa.
-What?
You must feed yourself well.
SAUCE BINS ARE FULL TOO
She has so many sauces.
You do have a thing for food.
-I'm quite obsessed.
-She does.
-Wow.
-Whoa.
-There are so many things.
-She has lots of stuff.
-It's completely different from ours.
-Let's go through it.
The top shelf.
I see.
-I see. The top shelf.
-What is it?
This kimchi is completely dried up.
You left it there?
-Wait.
-It hasn't been long since she had it.
HARDENED ON THE PLATE
-It has hardened.
-It has.
This one is sitting out here too.
This is a lot,
but do you keep it out in the open?
Yes, and when I crave some,
I flip it over and eat it.
Yes, that makes it new.
-Flip it like this.
-Flip it like this, and it's new.
-She's right.
-It's as good as new.
You've watched us since the first episode,
so you must know that
we show everything as is.
But here's the thing.
It was quite realistic for a few episodes
after the first one.
Then I began to see good ingredients
and clean fridges.
-Yes.
-It didn't feel used.
So I swore to show my real fridge
if I ever got to be on the show.
THAT'S THE SPIRIT…
That was what I had on my mind.
What's here?
-She has some peppers.
-Peppers.
Do you like spicy food?
-Aren't these really hot?
-Are those Thai chilies?
-Vietnamese chilies.
-Yes, bird's eye chilies.
We love spicy food so much
and eat it
until it probably ruins our stomachs.
-Whoa.
-Spicy food, I mean.
-That's like us.
-Those who love spicy food…
-…add Cheongyang pepper to everything.
-Yes.
-We always do that.
-Always.
-We need them before we have a bite.
-A spoon, a pepper.
It gets your appetite going.
HOW ADORABLE
Do you two like spicy food?
-Yes.
-So much. We love it.
In Africa,
there are these circular chilies,
and they're insanely spicy.
Really spicy.
-Habanero.
Are Cheongyang peppers like a snack?
FLEXING SPICE TOLERANCE
When I feel like having a snack.
It's like candy.
FLEXING ON ANOTHER LEVEL
-Like candy?
-It's that mild for you?
It's like chewing gum.
-Like candy.
-In that case,
let's do a test.
Let's see who's better with spicy food,
the sisters or the siblings.
You're eating that raw?
I'll give you one each.
-Nossamjang?
-I'm not as good anymore.
A BITE OF CHEONGYANG PEPPER
-That's spicy.
-It must be spicy.
That's a disaster.
Wait, is this Cheongyang pepper?
It is.
It doesn't taste spicy.
-"Crunchy Cheongyang pepper."
-It's not spicy.
-It's not spicy at all.
-Not at all.
It's spicy.
She says it's spicy.
-May I smell it? It's not spicy?
-No.
SNIFF
It smells pungent.
It's not a big deal?
POONG GIVES IT A TRY
Still, it looks like
that family has a higher spice tolerance.
It's spicy.
It's the spicy kind. It's really spicy.
Why don't we move on to these?
-Yes, I'd love to.
-Really?
-Get some water ready.
-Okay.
-It's…
-Is it that spicy?
ONE BIRD'S EYE CHILI EACH
SUNG-JU HAS TRIED IT IN EPISODE 10
WHOA!
HE COULDN'T STAND THE SPICINESS
-It's my first time.
-It's spicy.
HOW WILL JONATHAN & PATRICIA TAKE IT?
What's Vietnamese chili like?
-It's not a big deal.
-What?
-You have to chew on it.
-No, I'm serious.
-It's not that spicy. Really.
-No?
-Those are spicy.
-They're really spicy.
-Those are spicy. Oh, my eyes.
IN A RUSH
It's just pleasantly spicy.
-It feels like Cheongyang pepper.
-It does.
IT'S COMING…
BIBI's feeling it.
-Are you okay?
-Are you?
She's good with spicy food
but not compared to them.
-What's wrong? Water?
-What is it?
What are you looking for? Milk.
-Her mouth is burning.
-BIBI is on the weaker side.
-Did you check the expiry date?
-No idea.
BEGINS TO GULP
These two seem completely fine.
-Give us something spicier.
-They're tough.
What's here?
Mala xiang guo sauce.
INGREDIENTS FROM BIBI & NAKYOUNG'S FRIDGE:
MALA XIANG GUO SAUCE
-We make malatang at home.
-We love mala.
And the stir-fry.
Even hot pot. We like to dip things.
We like everything pungent
like chili, onion, garlic,
and green onion.
-The spicy and tangy things.
-And wasabi.
Buldak sauce.
They have lots of spicy sauces
on this side.
Hot sauce.
I like the feeling
when your tongue goes numb.
Something stimulating.
What's this? Meljeot.
Three tubs of anchovy aekjeot.
-We love jeotgal.
-I love all jeotgal.
These are quite salty.
I just put that on rice and eat it.
-We do that.
-Over white rice?
It's amazing with pork belly.
That's why we have it.
It's really good
when mixed with pepper and garlic.
I think she has kimchi on this side.
-Green onion kimchi?
-I recently got it from someone.
Who gave it to you?
This old lady that I know.
-An old lady that you know?
-Do you like this?
I love green onion.
I need that to eat with Chapaghetti.
-I can't live without kimchi.
-She can't.
The third shelf.
I see Western ingredients.
She has lots of Western ingredients
like cheese.
You have a variety of cheese.
What's this?
-It's called heart of palm.
-Yes, it says that.
-Heart of palm.
-Like pickles?
-From a palm tree.
-The core of a palm tree.
It's the core of a palm tree.
Can this be used as food?
It's considered
a premium ingredient in Western cuisine.
What does it taste like?
Or is it mostly for texture?
It's soft yet crunchy.
-Like bamboo shoots?
-Like artichokes.
Yes, and bamboo shoots.
What's this? Guanciale?
-She has guanciale?
-You have lots of Western ingredients.
She has guanciale?
Yes, because I love carbonara pasta.
Gosh, seriously.
-Actual carbonara pasta.
-Guanciale?
Not the fake ones. The real deal.
People often use bacon, but you need
guanciale to make the real one.
-And tomato sauce.
-I see.
Do you make pasta often?
I see lots of noodles here.
INGREDIENTS FROM BIBI & NAKYOUNG'S FRIDGE:
PASTA NOODLES
We make pasta often.
It's easy to make. Just toss it.
-It's easy to make?
-It's easy.
What do people say about your pasta?
It's really good. Whenever she makes it,
it's seasoned perfectly.
She has a knack for cooking.
When you watched our show avidly,
-did you try our recipes too?
-I often did. Thanks for your service.
FEELING PROUD
"Thanks for your service."
She watched us and learned to cook.
A singer Chef & My Fridge has raised.
A singer whom chefs have brought up.
I see some cutlassfish.
CUTLASSFISH
Stalked sea squirt.
-I love stalked sea squirt.
-Those are for NaKyoung.
AN UNEXPECTED TASTE IN FOOD
I love the smell so much.
-I love it too.
-I hate stalked sea squirt.
When you order fish soup for delivery,
there's stalked sea squirt inside, right?
-I eat it all.
-Stalked sea squirt?
It pops in your mouth.
Do you eat the shell too?
I eat it all. I swallow it whole.
You lived in Busan and Ulsan,
so you must love seafood.
-Yes, seafood was a staple.
-Mostly seafood.
Raw conger eel.
-Steamed monkfish.
-Steamed monkfish. We ate that so often.
Steamed monkfish? I've never had it.
-My dad fishes.
-Your dad fishes?
-Out in the sea?
-Does he still do it?
Yes, and I tag along.
I see.
-And grab a drink of soju?
-Of course.
I see it right here.
-You have the red caps, stronger ones.
-The red caps.
-Isn't it simply more delicious?
-It's stronger.
I always thought
the red caps tasted better.
In the end, alcohol itself
doesn't taste that good.
-Right.
-But you can
get drunk more easily
with the same amount.
Isn't that a win?
-More efficient?
-It's not about the taste.
That's what adults thought
in the old days.
So I like my drinks
up in the forty-something proof.
How much alcohol can you take?
One bottle of the red cap.
-One bottle.
-And NaKyoung?
One bottle of red cap,
and for the green one, two.
-They can take their alcohol.
-You're tough.
That's tough. How scary.
And down here,
some vegetables. I see some lettuce.
And water parsley? Do you like these?
-She loves them.
-Those are mine.
I love water parsley so much.
-Don't you love the smell?
-It's great.
It's great with braised monkfish.
It's a must.
So they like veggies too.
Now, down here in the freezer.
I see lots of seafood.
-Mackerel. Cutlassfish. Shrimp.
-Shrimp.
But these aren't prepped.
I love the texture of it,
so I always eat the heads and the tails
while NaKyoung eats the meat.
When I was younger,
I had this idea
that she was only into the tails.
So I'd eat the meat
and give her only the tails.
But I still need
a bit of meat on it, right?
But she had eaten every bit of the flesh.
She thought you only liked the tails.
But it was so cute, though.
-Here.
-She'd be eating over there,
-then she'd run up and go, "BIBI, tails."
-"BIBI loves tails."
She often gave me the tails like that.
-She went that far?
-Yes.
So I like food with a good texture.
What about fried chicken?
As for the drumsticks,
I don't eat the meat, but the tips.
-What? Just the tips?
-Just the tips?
-The crunchy part.
-The cartilage.
It's the cartilage.
I only like the cartilages.
That's unusual.
-I hope they sell just the cartilages.
-Fried cartilages.
I guess you'd never fight over food.
-You both like different things.
-Right.
What about you two?
It's like the remote control incident.
It's the same logic.
-I have to go for it first.
-Whoever gets it wins.
The drumsticks?
When the delivery comes,
it's usually the person
who goes out to get it.
Yes, that's the winner.
We grab it outside the door.
-We tamper with it first.
-Tamper.
You're competing all the time.
-Every moment. We never get a break.
-It's a battle.
Next, the meat.
-Beef.
Pork belly.
-You have lots of pork skin.
-What's this?
Pork skin sounds so good!
A BATCH OF PORK FAT
I watched this YouTuber
enjoying pork fat so much.
-Just the fat? It's good.
-Yes.
So I bought it, thinking it was one chunk,
but I got three.
I now have no idea what to do with that.
Why don't you…
-You can always give it to us.
-You can give it to us.
-Tell us how to eat it, and we'll do that.
-We got it.
-Are you asking the chefs to cook with it?
-Yes, that would be wonderful.
Shelf-stable products.
You really do love these things.
-Hot pot ingredients.
-Yes.
That's all for BIBI and NaKyoung's fridge!
Wow.
I wonder
what they're looking to eat today.
Let's find out their orders. Show us!
These are BIBI and NaKyoung's orders.
They both popped up together.
Spicy Sisters' Fiery Make-up Food.
-We always make up over tteokbokki.
-Making up.
We want our fight to be forgotten
because the food
is painfully spicy.
So we wanted to ask you to make that.
THE END OF PRESENTATION!
Gyeongsang-do Sisters' Soul Food.
We're sisters who grew up
on the coasts of South Gyeongsang-do,
so having hoe, raw fish fillet,
and soju is our thing.
TRUE THAT!
So I want to ask you to make something
that'll make us go,
-"It's the real deal!"
-I see.
When it comes to sisters,
we got the double high beams.
-You should probably join.
-Yes.
The high beams of Geumjeong-dong are in.
Spicy Sisters' Fiery Make-up Food.
My sister and I
also often had spicy food as we made up.
It's the perfect round for me.
The high beams of Geumjeong-dong
join the first one.
-Ho-young?
-Hey.
I'll make their makeup food.
SURPRISED
-Spicy food?
-I thought he'd go for seafood.
I know I can make a good spicy dish.
I thought you'd go for seafood.
Are you good with spicy food?
I never eat my meals
unless I have Cheongyang peppers.
What? Really?
-Ho-young's in.
-He eats well regardless of that.
Four bowls of rice with pepper
and three without.
So the spicy round has been decided.
Eun-yeong versus Ho-young.
Gyeongsang-do Sisters' Soul Food,
the seafood round.
I'll go.
The seafood round?
Whenever I come up with the menu
at my restaurant,
it's about 80 to 90% seafood.
CHOI HYUN-SUK WILL HANDLE THIS ROUND
So Hyun-suk suddenly joins the next round.
Who can beat him?
I will.
RISING EXPECTATIONS
I like the sound of seafood,
and she has the most abundant ingredients.
I couldn't miss the chance.
You should seize your chance
to cook with these.
So the chefs with many stars
joined the second round.
-It's a big match.
-It is.
Let us begin
Eun-yeong and Ho-young's round first.
Go.
The first round of cook-off played with
BIBI and NaKyoung's ingredients.
They're the dancing siblings of the show.
The dancing machine,
the older brother, Chef Jung Ho-young,
versus the ball of lunacy,
the younger sister, Chef Park Eun-yeong.
We have a record of something
that Eun-yeong has said.
"Someone like Chef Ho-young
is no longer in my league."
TAUNTING AGGRESSIVELY
"Someone like that"?
-Yes.
-Ho-young and I are often paired as rivals
because we both dance often.
But take a look
at Chef Ho-young's moves,
which are heavy and clumsy.
-"Heavy and clumsy"?
I don't think he's in my league.
A CHEF DISCUSSING DANCE SKILLS
His moves aren't so sharp.
I wouldn't say his moves are accurate.
She became kind of smug
after going viral with that one thing,
the Meatball Queen.
But I've spent many years dancing.
-Of course.
-If she wants to beat me,
she needs a few more years.
He's right about that.
He has been dancing since the days
when people said, "What's wrong with him?"
People were like, "Why does he do that?"
-Back when no chefs ever danced.
-Exactly.
-He danced back then.
-He started back then.
-He has paved the way.
-That's true.
They're arguing that Eun-yeong got here
because Ho-young started it all.
What's more urgent at this point
is for you two to make peace
instead of BIBI and NaKyoung.
But it doesn't look like
Eun-yeong wants to make up with him.
Not only does she think
she's a better dancer,
but she also thinks
the order is pretty much for her.
I know very well
how sisters make up over spicy food
through my 30 years of experience
with my sister.
I really know that all I have to do
is make something very spicy for them.
After all, Ho-young can't be sisters.
I can't be sisters with someone,
but I really love spicy food.
I pop Cheongyang peppers
into my mouth like popcorn.
I always keep it by my side.
I'd chew on one while watching TV.
He went way too far.
His pride in spice tolerance is a lie.
PICKING UP A CHEONGYANG PEPPER?
Is he serious?
WATCH ME
Hey, your face is turning red!
His cheeks are red.
BUT…
He's proving that he wasn't lying.
WHY DOES HE TAKE THINGS THAT FAR?
It must taste spicy.
-It must be.
-No, he doesn't find it spicy.
He has a hobby of whistling
after eating Cheongyang pepper.
He likes to whistle?
-It must be spicy.
-No, he likes to whistle.
-That's his hobby.
-Whistling.
A QUITE NICHE HOBBY
-It looks spicy.
-It's not that it's spicy.
No, it's not spicy at all.
He has a habit of whistling
after eating Cheongyang peppers.
CHEF EUN-YEONG'S INGREDIENTS:
PORK FAT, SOJU, BAY LEAF, BEECH MUSHROOM
CABBAGE, WATER PARSLEY, CHEONGYANG PEPPER,
MALA SEASONING OIL, OYSTER SAUCE, AND MORE
What are you making, Chef Eun-yeong?
The name of my dish is…
HIGH HOPES
…Red Flavor, Curious, Mala.
It seemed like
you two were into the taste of mala.
You had lots of ingredients
from Sichuan in the fridge,
so I want to make
one of Sichuan's famous dishes,
Sichuan water-poached meat, shuizhu beef.
-Water-poached beef.
-Yes.
It's a dish where you boil meat
in spicy and hot soup.
BIBI also mentioned
she couldn't find good use
for the pork fat,
-Yes.
-…which came with the skin.
I'll boil the pork skin nicely
and make a spicy salad
using NaKyoung's favorite, water parsley.
-A spicy set meal, so to speak.
-It also came with skin?
CHEF HO-YOUNG'S INGREDIENTS:
TENDERLOIN, PORK BELLY, SWEET PUMPKIN
STALKED SEA SQUIRT, BIRD'S EYE CHILI,
CHEONGYANG PEPPER, POLLACK ROE, AND MORE
What are you making, Ho-young?
Though you didn't have short ribs,
I'll use pork belly and beef tenderloin
to make spicy galbi-jjim,
braised short ribs,
with green onion kimchi.
-And then,
-Green onion kimchi?
…NaKyoung likes stalked sea squirt,
so I'll make a bibimbap with it.
-And…
-Stalked sea squirt bibimbap?
-I've never heard of it.
-…I'll turn them into tiny rice balls
to make it easier to eat with galbi-jjim.
In just 15 minutes?
HIGH FIVE
Let us begin the round,
"Spicy Sisters' Fiery Make-up Food."
Give us the timer for 15 minutes.
-Whoa.
-This is legendary.
-No way.
We give them only 15 minutes.
It's really 15 minutes.
Here to take down Ho-young
with her experience
from fighting her older sister,
the high beams of Geumjeong-dong,
Chef Park Eun-yeong.
Here to make Eun-yeong cry a river,
the fiery spatula of Yeonhui-dong,
Chef Jung Ho-young.
Which one of them will capture
the spicy sisters' appetite?
Let the 15-minute cook-off begin!
ALREADY FIRED UP IN EXCITEMENT
THIS ROUND IS SO HOT
Make something spicy for them.
You can see everything.
-We can see it.
-The timer has started.
We can actually see them.
You begin just like that?
It was the real deal.
I have to do well today.
-She's grabbing the pork fat.
-Right away?
-Yes, the pork fat.
-She has to remove the skin.
Her knife looks so cool.
I've never seen that.
-It's a Chinese kitchen knife.
-Really?
She's removing the pork skin.
So she's making salad with that?
Yes, it's delicious
once you boil it and season it.
My gosh.
-It won't be easy.
-In 15 minutes?
It'll be tough.
She's doing that first
because it takes time to cook.
She poured soju into the pot
to remove the fat smell.
WOW!
BEGINS WITH THE TENDERLOIN
He's prepping the meat first.
1. CHOP TENDERLOIN
INTO BITE-SIZED PIECES AND GRILL
WHAT'S NEXT?
Ho-young grabs pork belly.
-I love pork belly.
-Beef and pork?
I'm using pork belly.
He's going to braise it,
so he threw it into a pressure cooker.
ONION, GREEN ONION, GARLIC
He's so fast.
INTO THE COOKER
-Sweet pumpkin.
My makeup artist's parents
grew that themselves.
I see.
-It's really good.
-They grew that themselves.
-"Sweet, oh so sweet, sweet pumpkin."
-You're right.
Sweet, oh so sweet, sweet pumpkin.
PORK SKIN, OUT
-Look at that pork skin.
-It's cooked already?
-I'll cook it in a pressure cooker.
-A pressure cooker.
-I see. The skin.
-Right. If she uses a pressure cooker,
it'll get rid of that fat smell.
She's making use of a pressure cooker.
She's steaming pork skin
in the pressure cooker.
BEECH MUSHROOM
I love mushrooms.
Especially oyster mushrooms.
Eun-yeong grabs mushrooms
-and cabbage.
-Cabbage.
Are you putting the cabbage
underneath the pork?
I'm putting it into the hot pot.
Into the hot pot.
PREPPING THE VEGGIES
It's been three minutes.
Wow.
Ho-young is making sauce.
OYSTER SAUCE
SUGAR, VINEGAR
He's adding lots of red pepper powder.
-That looks spicy.
-It does.
He's pouring the sauce in there.
It looks so red.
-Whoa. It looks spicy.
-It looks so spicy.
GETTING EXCITED
SUDDEN DISTANCE
Are you braising that too?
Yes, I'll have the pork belly
braised so it's tender,
then top it with grilled beef tenderloin.
It smells so good.
-Water parsley.
-Water parsley?
-NaKyoung's favorite.
-Water parsley.
NaKyoung's favorite, water parsley.
-It's Eun-yeong.
-Water parsley.
Cheongyang pepper.
TO ADD SPICINESS
Yes, add some chili peppers.
4. PREP WATER PARSLEY, CHEONGYANG PEPPER,
GARLIC, THEN MIX WITH MALA OIL
-That one has to be good.
-It has to be.
They're both so quick.
They really are.
Stalked sea squirt…
-Do you need help?
-A bit.
ON MY WAY
What are you up to now, Sam?
-He just took something up.
-Prepping the stalked sea squirt.
He's cutting off the tips.
-Removing the innards.
-One at a time?
Ho-young said
he'd make bibimbap with that.
I've never had stalked sea squirt
out of the shell.
-I see.
-Shell-less stalked sea squirt.
Shell-less stalked sea squirt.
SLAM
She's so quick.
DESTROYING GARLIC
-I've never seen anything like it.
-She's crushing the garlic.
-How cool.
-Lots of garlic.
Green onion.
How is she so good with the knife?
And she's really fast.
-I'd cut off my hand.
-At that speed, she must be
willing to sacrifice her hand.
DON'T BE SO SURPRISED YET
-There it is. Mala sauce.
-Mala sauce!
-The red flavor!
-Eun-yeong!
RED FLAVOR
Red flavor.
Eun-yeong's red flavor.
I'm smelling the mala now.
It's dark red.
It's probably spicier now.
-It's spicy now.
-Let's switch seats.
It seems really spicy.
It smells spicy.
THE ATTACK OF THE SPICY SMOKE
It's coming at us.
HOT WATER!
We're smelling the smoke now.
SPREAD, MALA SMOKE
-Whoa.
-That's spicy.
This isn't just regular old smoke!
It looks so good.
I'm so excited right now.
That's all pepper smoke.
-It's stinging my eyes too.
-Mine too.
My eyes sting.
-It stings.
-Like CBRN training.
WHAT ABOUT THE SPICY SISTERS?
It smells so delicious.
-It's a CBRN training.
-It smells so good.
-It smells good, though.
-I love it.
They look so happy.
-It smells so good.
-I'm drooling so much that I can't talk.
The sisters look absolutely excited.
YAY
ADDING MORE R-R-RED FLAVOR
MALA HOT POT SAUCE
That's strong.
-That's strong.
-Yes, that's strong.
That's strong.
You don't even eat spicy food.
I do.
I only eat spicy food.
-Oyster sauce?
-Oyster sauce.
Is that bird's eye chili, Eun-yeong?
Yes, I'm using them.
-She's adding the Vietnamese chili.
-Everything goes in.
She added them whole.
That looks really spicy.
EMERGENCY
That looks like an inferno.
It looks so spicy.
LICKING HER LIPS
You have under ten minutes left.
It smells so good.
What are you grinding, Ho-young?
PEPERONCINO
It looks like peperoncino.
He now has
Cheongyang peppers in his hands.
Cheongyang peppers.
Shouldn't you be
snacking on them as you cook?
LAUGHING
WHY NOT?
CRUNCHY PEPPER
He's serious about spicy food.
He even snacks on them as he cooks.
CRUNCHING
AND THE BIRD'S EYE CHILI
Whoa, hey!
That's going to kill you.
…WHAT DID I JUST WITNESS?
Why did you eat the red one?
COUGH…
YOU SAID YOU COULD TAKE THE SPICE
HE MUST'VE GONE WAY OVERBOARD…
Start whistling.
-Whistle.
-He's coughing.
CLEARING THROAT…
He ground the Cheongyang pepper.
Look at the amount of chili peppers.
I think he'll add them all.
-He's grabbing rice.
-He's making rice balls.
Sea squirt rice balls.
-Salted pollack roe?
-He adds salted pollack roe.
That has to be good.
CHOPPING SOMETHING…
-What's that?
-Shio kombu, kelp seasoning.
KELP SEASONING IN!
Did you add kelp seasoning, Ho-young?
Yes, I chopped
some kelp seasoning into the rice.
I love rice balls
made with kelp seasoning.
WATER PARSLEY
-He's adding water parsley too.
-That looks so good.
It's for the aroma and the texture.
That looks so good.
I can't take my eyes off both.
STARTING ON THE WATER-POACHED BEEF
What's the cut you're using, Eun-yeong?
-Tenderloin?
-Yes, beef tenderloin.
She can still answer
while she's busy cooking.
EGG
-Isn't Chef Eun-yeong really fast?
-The way her hands move.
5. MIX BEEF WITH EGG WASH AND STARCH
She's marinating beef
to make the water-poached beef.
-I see.
-It's to make the meat more tender.
-It goes into the oil.
-It's going into the oil?
What does that do?
-It makes the meat tender.
-It becomes very tender.
BIBI's quite interested in cooking.
I'll have to try it at home.
Cooking meat in the oil
will make it even more tender.
They only have six minutes left.
-Six minutes.
-Can they finish?
It's even fiercer in real life
compared to what's shown on TV.
Of course.
The camera doesn't do them justice.
It doesn't. It's a war here.
OPENS THE PRESSURE COOKER
He opens the cooker.
Ho-young opens the pressure cooker first.
Whoa. That's spicy.
-That's spicy.
-That one's spicy.
THAT'S MY DIFFUSER
-It smells good.
-But it smells good.
COUGHING
IT'S KILLING NAM-NO…
Look at Chef Nam-no.
It's spicy.
MOVING THE GALBI-JJIM INTO A PAN
-It's so red.
-It looks spicy.
Five and a half minutes.
It's probably spicier
than that famous spicy pork cutlet.
That'd kill you.
THESE CAN POTENTIALLY
MAKE THEM SICK AFTERWARD
They both look so red.
Hey! Wide glass noodles!
-Wide glass noodles!
-What are those noodles?
Wide glass noodles!
Wide glass noodles.
Young people love them.
-It's going to be so chewy.
-They must love them.
Sung-ju, can you go check on the kitchen?
Well, I'm kind of hesitant.
Please find out if those dishes
can help the sisters make up.
They look way too spicy.
-Please go check.
-What do I do?
Time to go!
STALKED SEA SQUIRT THAT "SOMEONE" PREPPED
3. MIX SEA SQUIRT WITH RICE
Eun-yeong and Ho-young's
spicy dish cook-off.
This one looks insane.
-Sung-ju.
-Yes?
Try the mala soup,
the one Eun-yeong made.
-I'm too scared.
-But you still have to do it.
It looks so scary.
Let me try just a sip.
No way. It's too spicy.
-It's probably very hot.
-I'll try it.
ARRRRGH!
What's it like?
My tongue feels numb.
That sounds great.
It numbs your tongue.
I can't eat the leftovers today.
My eyes are burning.
HO-YOUNG WON'T BACK DOWN!
He added lots of ground pepper too.
PEPERONCINO
-No, stop adding so much.
-Those?
He just stashed peperoncino in.
He added more chili peppers!
SPICY LEVEL GOES UP
-Try that one too.
-Red, red, Ho-young.
THE DEATH OF THE "RED RED" TREND
It looks red. Very red.
He's adorable.
-If you don't feel it, it's not too spicy.
-Right. If I do, it's spicier.
Does it taste red red?
IS THE GALBI-JJIM TOTALLY RED RED?
-You don't feel it?
-I guess it's not too spicy.
-Huh?
-He doesn't feel it.
There's a difference.
A different kind of spiciness?
This was spicy
from the moment it hit my mouth,
-but this one hits you later.
-Later?
I think I can handle this one.
ADDING STALKED SEA SQUIRT
Whoa, what was that?
RAN AWAY QUICKLY
-Warn us beforehand!
-Sorry about that.
She's saying you're talking too much.
HO-YOUNG'S DISH ISN'T AS SPICY
You said you liked spicy food,
but it wasn't even spicy enough for me.
EUN-YEONG WILL WIN, GREEN GREEN
The meat is ready.
It looks so good. Is that meat?
The cabbage will
probably reduce the spiciness.
Two minutes and twelve seconds.
-You haven't opened the pressure cooker.
-No.
Ho-young makes rice balls.
They look so pretty.
Look at the rice balls.
Those rice balls are so cute.
A LOAD OF SESAME OIL
7. MIX OIL WITH CRUSHED GARLIC,
VINEGAR, SUGAR, AND CHILI FLAKES
MAKING DIPS!
What now? I have to add this.
-There's still some pressure inside.
-It's not fully released.
GOING FOR A COLD SHOWER!
It's an emergency measure.
-Is this the side dish?
-Yes, with the pork skin.
I'll mix it with the pork skin.
The lid is off!
Eun-yeong managed to get the lid off.
Hurry up and mix them.
-Move quickly.
-It's still hot!
It's probably still hot.
She's mixing it with the veggies.
A minute and a half.
-Not much time left.
-Can they do this?
-What?
-Is this possible?
You don't have much time.
A minute and a half.
-Whoa. All that?
-He's adding more Cheongyang pepper.
You have about a minute now.
INTO A LARGE METAL BOWL
You don't have much time left.
The metal bowl.
That's spicy galbi-jjim, Daegu-style.
-I really love that.
-He's using a metal bowl.
It's in a metal bowl.
-Keep it up, Ho-young.
-That's insane.
You're doing great. It looks so good.
-Forty seconds.
-Spicy galbi-jjim.
She's using wide glass noodles too.
We really love glass noodles.
She's serving it in an earthen pot.
SHE'S USING AN EARTHEN POT
He's adding more?
ADD MORE PEPERONCINO
What about green onion kimchi?
-Yes, the green onion.
-The green onion kimchi.
THE CHERRY ON TOP, GREEN ONION KIMCHI
IT LOOKS INSANELY DELICIOUS
You would've forgotten
if I hadn't mentioned it.
-It would've been bad.
-Green onion kimchi.
Twenty-five seconds.
GREEN ONION KIMCHI, GALBI-JJIM, RED RED
IS DONE
He's done?
So this is how you make
the pork skin dish.
SESAME OIL, VINEGAR, SOY SAUCE
-Keep it up.
-It's a side dish.
-Fifteen seconds.
Once Eun-yeong finishes, that's it.
-Five.
-Four.
-Three. Two.
-One.
-The end.
-Time's up.
Eun-yeong finishes too.
Both chefs are done cooking.
THE RED-FLAVORED DISHES ARE FINISHED
-They really did it in 15 minutes.
-They did it in 15 minutes.
Did you think we lied?
-I mean, still.
-I thought you'd have a leeway.
No, when the time's up, it's done.
-Whoa.
That was too shocking.
It was.
Here they come.
THE FIERY MAKEUP DISHES ARE ON THEIR WAY
WOW
It smells so good.
-This mala diffuser.
-Diffuser.
Both chefs' dishes are finished
for BIBI and NaKyoung.
YAY
As a fan who has watched us
since our first episode,
what was it like to see them cook?
Despite the rules, I thought…
I thought you'd give
-a little more time.
-Yes.
But nothing at all.
It was 15 minutes and nothing more.
-Seriously.
-Yes, I was surprised to see it.
-I thought they could go, "Wait, timeout."
-No way.
Taking time off.
Things happen as you cook.
We're only humans.
True.
-At times, you can make a mistake.
-Yes.
Even if you threw in three more minutes,
you'd let it go
with the good old Korean love.
But they had to stop after 15 minutes.
So cutthroat.
-It's so transparent.
-Yes.
Ho-young was the first to finish
making those dishes for the sisters.
TRYING HO-YOUNG'S DISH FIRST
Please try that first.
RED RED GREEN ONION KIMCHI AND GALBI-JJIM
SALTY AND BRINY SEA SQUIRT RICE BALLS
CHEF JUNG HO-YOUNG'S
GREEN ONION KIMCHI, GALBI-JJIM, RED RED
-Thank you.
-Here's the thing.
-It's still hot. That's why.
-You can see the steam.
-How should they eat this?
-First of all,
wrap a piece of meat
with green onion kimchi
drenched in the soup.
-Wrap it around.
-Usually…
-I got it.
-…guests wait
until the chefs tell them
how to eat their dishes.
-Not them.
-They started serving it first.
-Have that first, and then the rice.
-And then the rice.
-I see.
-The spicy dish first.
She's serving it to her sister first.
She gave it to NaKyoung.
-How sweet.
-So nice.
-She's here to make peace with her.
-How nice.
-Are you trying to make peace?
THE SPICY SISTERS ARE MAKING UP
They remind me of my sister and me.
Wait, he added
wide glass noodles too, NaKyoung.
-I'm drooling so much.
-It looks spicy.
Wide glass noodles.
-Take a good look.
-I feel…
-I feel so rushed.
-She might take the bigger piece.
-Take off a few pieces.
-And telling her,
"That's the delicious part."
-It's the delicious part.
-Are you sure it's good?
You've grabbed lots of meaty pieces.
-This is punishment for us.
-It looks spicy.
-Thank you for the food.
-Now, time to try it.
Wow.
TOPPING TENDERLOIN
WITH A PIECE OF GREEN ONION KIMCHI
That's it.
Wrap a piece of meat with kimchi.
TAKING A BITE TOGETHER
Red, red.
LOVES HIS JOKES♥
I wonder how spicy it is for them.
Look at BIBI go.
-It's good.
-It is?
There is this
-odd balance.
-I see.
What if he forgot
to add the green onion kimchi?
-It's sweet, salty, and spicy.
-Yes.
It's not just spicy. It's sweet too.
But it's not overly sweet.
It just makes you go,
"It's spicy."
"It's sweet too." Like that.
-It's so hard to watch.
-It's so good.
It feels so comforting.
A soul food.
-I see.
-It's worthy of making peace.
ANOTHER BIG BITE
-Spicy galbi-jjim comes with sweetness.
-I see.
-It's not as good if it's just spicy.
-I need rice.
He made good use
of the green onion kimchi.
Go for the rice balls.
YOU'RE RIGHT
-Go for it when you crave rice.
-That's also spicy too.
-Isn't it spicy?
-It must be.
-Patricia.
-Yes?
Wipe your mouth.
-My gosh.
-Your mouth was open too wide.
HER MOUTH IS FLOODING
Can you wipe the table too?
They both eat so well.
Sea squirt rice balls.
It smells like stalked sea squirt.
That's new.
I'm not really into stalked sea squirt,
-but this is somewhat…
-She said NaKyoung liked it.
-I added some pollack roe.
-Yes, salted pollack roe.
-Then added stalked sea squirt too.
-They go so well.
It has a pleasant briny smell.
-A pleasant briny smell.
-Subtle.
What about the spiciness?
I can take something even spicier,
-but this is something I can enjoy.
-Something close to normal.
-Something that normal humans eat.
-It's humanely tolerable.
-"Humanely tolerable"?
CRUNCH
-Did you add stalked sea squirt to this?
-I did.
I can hear the crunchy sound.
-It sounds so delicious.
-It's so good.
Does the kimchi play a part?
-It's so important.
-It is?
Its pungent flavor is the kick.
THE SPICY SISTERS WON'T STOP
They're tiny, yet they eat so well.
They don't even stop for a second.
-And she eats it in one bite.
-She eats well.
JEALOUS…
DROOLING
This is almost torture.
-What's wrong?
-What is it?
I thought you were here to give us food.
-I thought he came to give it to us.
-Really.
-Water-poached beef is turning into jerky.
-Right.
-Eun-yeong is up next.
-Eun-yeong's dish remains.
-You have to eat that too.
-You must.
-We can eat it all.
-You can eat more later.
All right.
FEELING PROUD
NEXT, EUN-YEONG'S DISH
WATER-POACHED BEEF WITH A DEEP RED FLAVOR
SESAME OIL SAUCE
TO BRING OUT THE BEEFY FLAVOR
PORK SKIN SALAD WITH LOTS OF WATER PARSLEY
CHEF PARK EUN-YEONG'S
RED FLAVOR, CURIOUS, MALA
You can dip the beef
in the sauce in front of you.
When people go to hot pot places,
many Koreans like to dip the food
into peanut or sesame sauce.
But in Sichuan, it's sesame oil,
vinegar, salt, and garlic.
-I see.
-Whoa.
-Thank you.
What's this red flavor like?
It was different
from Ho-young's spiciness.
-It was something Gen MZ would love.
-This one.
This is Chinese spiciness,
and Ho-young's is Korean spiciness.
-Yes, that's the difference.
-Yes.
-Was it much spicier?
-It must be spicier.
Why are you looking at her? What is it?
-It must be spicy.
-What is it, BIBI?
-It's spicy.
-It is?
-But it's so good. It's aromatic.
-Aromatic?
It smells so good.
A BITE OF THE GLASS NOODLE
SLURP
EXHILARATED
-That's it.
-She likes it.
-It must be good.
-It has to be good.
We call this Jang Won-young glass noodles.
-Have you heard of it?
-It's hot.
It's different
from the glass noodles we eat.
What's Jang Won-young glass noodles?
-Something that Won-young likes?
-Is it spicy?
But I like those too.
HAHA
-Kim Poong glass noodles.
-I like them too.
Why do you call it that?
It's a neologism, I think.
-What?
-It's like
the opposite of bamti, "tacky,"
Jang Won-young.
-It's the opposite of bamti?
-It's the antonym of bamti?
When something's really great,
like some shoes you love,
you call them Jang Won-young shoes.
Something that's great.
I'll start using that.
What's bamti?
Is it chestnut tiramisu, bam tiramisu?
LOL
People use that word
to call stuff that's awful.
Something that isn't great.
BAMTI: NEOLOGISM FOR UGLY, TACKY, LOUSY
-I thought it was bam tiramisu.
-No.
TOP IT WITH SESAME OIL SAUCE
YUM
Mmm.
Eun-yeong.
-Do you like the sauce?
-It hits you
just as the dish
is about to get almost too spicy.
It comes in and covers your mouth
with sourness and nuttiness.
-So it plays a big part?
-Yes.
I'm sorry, but I'm craving a drink.
-You're craving a drink?
-It calls for a drink.
It calls for a drink?
There are different levels
of spiciness for malatang, right?
From level one to even four or five.
This has gone way over level five.
-I see.
-It's even spicier?
-It's about level seven.
-Really?
It must be really spicy.
-We're okay with it.
-It's great.
It looks like you're sweating a little.
But after eating something this spicy
and sweating it out,
-you'd forget about the fight.
-I would forget.
WHY THE CHOPSTICKS?
Excuse me. Please do not eat the metal.
OH MY MY
-Don't eat it.
-Why did you pick them up?
-Calm down.
-You're going to love this.
They don't even care.
A BITE OF PORK SKIN SALAD
RESPONDS IMMEDIATELY
THIS IS INSANE!
LOVE THE SALAD
There's a big frenzy over here.
-The pork skin.
-They're going crazy over the pork skin.
Who made this?
Seriously. It's so good.
Tell them what you meant by
"Who made this?"
What's that?
-What's "pomeki?"
-It's "who made this."
When you eat something really good,
you get mad and go, "Who made this?"
-"Who made this?"
-Because it was so good.
Who made this?
-Who made this?
Then the chef will feel alarmed.
"Is there something wrong?"
"It's so good!"
"It's dang good!"
All these Gen MZ know what it is.
Who made this?
-So good!
HAVE WE PUT ANOTHER MEME TO REST?
They're going crazy over this.
EATING UP THE SALAD
They're crazy about the pork skin.
I don't like anything that tastes sour.
-I see.
-Yes?
But it's just sour enough
to feel pleasant.
It tastes so pleasant.
It smells and feels great too.
What is this? Prickly ash?
You had this mala-flavored oil.
So I mixed that with vinegar,
sugar, and soy sauce.
-She's good at this.
-And water parsley.
Is the pork skin cooked well?
-It's tender.
-And chewy.
You've cooked it well.
THE SIBLINGS CONTINUE TO DROOL…
Want some?
-Yes!
-Please, if we may.
Do you want some?
-Yes.
-We want some!
-Then scream!
-Yes!
Give us some!
APPROVED
"Give us some!"
-Give us some!
-Give them some.
This is Chef Ho-young's dish.
-Try the meat with kimchi.
-The meat.
-Whoa.
-I'll try some.
THE SPICINESS MADE HIM SUDDENLY AGE
-It's spicy.
-With kimchi.
PATRICIA TAKES A SPICY BITE TOO
-Mmm.
-I can't do this.
It's good. It's so good.
-Isn't it good?
-Is this okay?
EVERYTHING AT ONCE
IN ONE BITE
-Isn't it spicy?
-No, not at all.
Not at all?
BREAKING OUT IN A SWEAT
JONATHAN BEGINS TO DEVOUR IT TOO
IMMEDIATELY POPS A RICE BALL IN
-The pork tastes great.
-It's spicy.
I've never seen Nam-no
having trouble with food.
-I'm not good with spicy food.
-Oh, no.
It's really good,
-but my tongue can't handle it.
-It can't?
SAM'S SOUL HAS LEFT HIM TOO
It's a shame
that you can't eat something this good.
Man, I give up.
You can see the effect.
But this rice ball? Who made this?
-It's so good.
-Yes, who made this?
Nathan, you can never eat anything fishy.
I'm not big on seafood,
-but it doesn't taste fishy at all.
-You don't even eat sea squirt.
-I mixed it with perilla oil.
-It was perilla oil.
I know that
this is going to mess with me later,
but I can't stop eating it.
-You keep craving it.
-It's not too spicy.
Next, Chef Eun-yeong's dish.
YUM
Thank you.
-Mmm.
-It's not spicy.
It's not too spicy.
-You have a high spice tolerance.
-It's not that.
You're just not used
to the spiciness of mala.
The spiciness isn't that bad.
PICKING ON IT
DROPPING THE SOUP…
Eun-yeong's dish looks insanely spicy too.
Sam's only pretending to try it.
SURPRISED SAM
LOL
Try it already.
-You can see it from there?
-Yes.
PRETENDING TO EAT IT
I had it. It's too spicy.
Tell us what it was like.
I don't understand…
It's incomprehensible to me.
"Why do people want this?"
Ho-young's dish made my heart spicy,
but Eun-yeong's dish fired up my mouth.
-You're right. Exhilaration.
-Simply put, yes.
A BITE OF THE PORK SKIN SALAD
-Mmm.
-This is good.
This is good.
-Water parsley salad is great, right?
-It's such a kick.
When you bite on the pork skin
along with the water parsley,
it spreads all over your mouth.
MOUTH FULL OF WATER PARSLEY AROMA
-It pops in your mouth with every bite.
-Water parsley.
"Water parsley. I'm water parsley."
"I'm water parsley."
-"I'm water parsley"?
-That happens in your mouth.
It's now time to choose.
-It must be hard.
-Pick up the remote control.
If you pick the same chef, that's it.
-But if you don't, you'll talk it out.
-It's tough.
Press one to choose Park Eun-yeong
and two for Jung Ho-young.
BIBI and NaKyoung, make your choice
and press the button.
The two sisters' choice.
They haven't talked yet.
-They both picked one.
-They did?
The verdict is out.
Their choices were
different.
It's a tie.
Really?
1:1, A TIE
Most sisters would choose the same thing.
-They chose different chefs.
-No way.
Then we'll give you some time to chat.
-Come here.
-But talk quietly.
-Where are we going?
-Where to?
Don't let BIBI make the decision.
Have a good discussion.
"You have to listen to me."
"Number one is better."
BIBI always had more power
over the remote control.
-Okay.
-Good.
-We're done talking.
-You are? All right.
This is the final decision.
Please press the button.
One for Eun-yeong, two for Ho-young.
BIBI WILL CHOOSE FOR THE TWO OF THEM
The result is in.
Whose opinion had a bigger impact?
Let's find out their decision.
Show us!
Spicy Sisters' Fiery Make-up Food.
Ho-young's Korean spiciness
versus Eun-yeong's Chinese spiciness.
Which side did they choose?
Is it Ho-young
or Eun-yeong?
Who did BIBI and NaKyoung choose?
JUNG HO-YOUNG WINS
It was Ho-young.
GREEN ONION KIMCHI,
GALBI-JJIM, RED RED WINS
KOREAN SPICINESS WINS
I actually thought it would be
-an easy win for the mala dish.
-Me too.
The pork skin was so delicious.
-I first chose Chef Eun-yeong.
-And I, Chef Ho-young.
But NaKyoung said,
"Which one would you eat every day?"
Both dishes were so good.
They'll have to fight daily.
1 FIGHT AND 1 FOOD TO MAKE UP EACH DAY
The fight galbi.
-It can cause discord within the family.
-Probably.
Congratulations, Chef Ho-young!
JUNG HO-YOUNG, GREEN GREEN
-It was so good.
-He wins
against Chef Eun-yeong
and takes his ninth star. Congrats!
Congratulations, Ho-young.
Let us begin the second cook-off
with BIBI and NaKyoung's ingredients.
The two good-looking chefs.
The older brother with a great physique,
Chef Choi Hyun-suk.
GREAT PHYSIQUE
The sexy grandpa.
The younger brother with good looks
and good vibes, Chef Son Jong-won.
Jong-won.
Did you say this order is special to you?
Is there a reason?
Gyeongsang-do, especially Ulsan,
has a special place in my heart.
-Is it another hometown?
-He has too many hometowns.
One of the biggest reasons
why I got into culinary arts
was the time
when I went to Ulsan with my dad
and had fresh hoe, fish fillet,
right from the sea.
I realized how powerful it was
to eat something in its origin.
I wanted to start sharing that
with my customers.
-I had this idea when I was six.
-Six?
-Age six?
-Kids that young don't eat raw fish.
-It's like my second hometown as a chef.
-His second hometown.
-He has too many hometowns.
-Because of hoe?
-Too many hometowns.
-He's doing that again to win a star.
Is it because
we're doing a sibling special?
We received lots of heartwarming stories.
-What is it?
-Chef Jong-won picked Hyun-suk
as the chef he wanted
to have as an older brother.
-As an older brother?
-Is there a special reason?
I'm an only child,
so I was always jealous
of friends who had an older brother.
When I joined the show,
he was considerate like a brother,
welcomed me warmly,
complimented me often, and always showed
the biggest laughter at my lousy jokes.
He can't hide his smile.
CAN'T HIDE HIS HAPPINESS
He's 12 years older than you,
so he's more like an uncle.
It'd be odd to call him hyeong.
Can he call you that?
If someone like Jong-won
would call me hyeong,
I can give him everything I have,
even my organs.
Do it and take it all.
I believe your organs aren't too healthy.
His gall bladder isn't making bile liquid.
Jong-won doesn't need it.
-It's useless.
-It won't be much help.
I thought he'd give me his
if I gave him mine. Happy now?
AS ALWAYS, IT'S FUN TO TEASE HIM
Well, he wants to call you hyeong,
so why don't you do that
and say what you want to?
ALREADY FEELS AWKWARD
Hyun-suk hyeong.
Go easy on me.
SMILING
-"Go easy on me."
Jong-won also said this.
"Chef Hyun-suk is the pillar of the show."
You said that?
Why are you so nice to him?
No matter what we do to tease him,
he's always a good sport about it.
That's true.
But because of his age,
the pillar has been tilted a little.
Like the Tower at Pisa?
It's going sideways.
-But he holds out.
-He does.
Well, as long as he holds out.
Thank you for your kind words.
But this show is as wild as the savanna.
Whenever I am
frolicking around like a gazelle,
Jung-hwan would come
like a lion and bite my neck.
So while I'm in pain,
someone like Ho-young comes along
and nibbles on my offal.
-It's the best part.
-It's delicious.
He's yummy.
But while you're hunted down,
the one who shows the biggest laughter
-is Chef Jong-won.
-Right.
-He loves it.
-He really does.
He's like a tourist in a car
on a safari trip.
"He's getting hunted down."
"They're eating him so happily."
Jong-won had been quietly nibbling
on Hyun-suk in the shadows.
This place is a jungle.
CHEF HYUN-SUK'S INGREDIENTS:
SHRIMP, CUTLASSFISH, SEA SQUIRT
FLYING FISH ROE, SCALLOP, OYSTER SAUCE,
WATER PARSLEY, PORK FAT, AND MORE
What are you making, Chef Hyun-suk?
The name of my dish is…
-Is cutlassfish your main ingredient?
-Yes.
I'll fillet the fish,
grind it with shrimp and pork fat,
make fish balls, and put them on a skewer.
And then, I'll make hearty broth
full of seafood
along with a Chinese-style
glass noodle stir-fry.
Glass noodle stir-fry?
HARD TO IMAGINE
I'm not a Chinese chef,
so I might need some of your help.
I'll help you. Don't worry.
-No, not you.
-I'll help.
Let me help. Don't worry.
Nobody help him. I got him.
Don't say anything. Don't move.
-What about me?
-No, Eun-yeong. I'll help.
Don't you dare come near me.
CHEF JONG-WON'S INGREDIENTS:
SHRIMP, SEA SQUIRT, MELJEOT, SCALLOP
COCONUT CREAM, WATER PARSLEY,
RICE PAPER, SPICY SNACK, AND MORE
What are you making, Jong-won?
I want to portray the spirit
of the Gyeongsang-do sisters
by using fresh seafood
right from the Ulsan sea.
It's called
BIBI, NaKyoung, as Real as Ever.
-As real as ever.
I kind of like the title.
-It's Gyeongsang dialect. As real as ever.
-As real as ever.
Do you still use dialect?
"It's quite hot."
HER DIALECT IS AS REAL AS EVER
I can actually speak like I'm from Seoul.
But when I'm with her,
it becomes rather tough to keep up.
-"Tough to keep up."
-Tough to keep up.
WE NOW LIVE IN SEOUL
I see. What's your dish like?
They had lots of special ingredients.
There's a variety of pasta
called conchiglie.
I want to make them look like escargot
-and fill them with scallop meat.
-With scallops?
Next, I'll use shrimp
and make it crispy with some rice paper.
In the previous round,
you seemed to be craving a drink,
-so I'll make a James Bond-style drink.
-James Bond?
-A dirty martini.
-A dirty martini?
-But with stalked sea squirt.
-Sea squirt dirty martini?
There's a hint of a cucumber-like smell
in stalked sea squirt, so I'll take that
and put it inside the heart of palm.
Then I'll blend soju
and create a perfectly balanced cocktail.
You're blending soju?
-They have different soju brands.
-Wait.
Can he do all that in 15 minutes?
It may not happen.
We cut them off right on time.
Then it'll just be dirty.
It'll take some points off.
-Not dirty martini?
-Just dirty.
Let us begin the actual round.
Gyeongsang-do Sisters' Soul Food.
-Wow.
-That's really cool.
-It's so cool.
He'll show the years of experience
as someone 12 years older,
Chef Choi Hyun-suk.
He'll devour Hyun-suk
until the very last bite,
Chef Son Jong-won.
Which one of the chefs will fill
BIBI and NaKyoung's souls?
Let the 15-minute cook-off begin!
Wow.
-Gyeongsang-do's soul food.
-Two good chefs.
Can you peel the shrimp?
Peel the shrimp for me.
A DISCREET MOVE
Seafood is everything.
-He's prepping shrimp.
-Prepping shrimp.
Hyun-suk rarely ever makes
anything Chinese-inspired.
These sisters are from Gyeongsang-do.
Pasta.
And shrimp.
It'll take a while for that pasta to cook.
PULLS OUT A TIMER
-Ten minutes until al dente.
-Ten minutes.
He's boiling the shrimp.
And straight into cold water.
It's to peel them off easily.
To peel them off.
So it's easier to peel them off
if you put them in cold water?
Cutlassfish.
-It's cutlassfish.
-He's cutting it
to remove just the meat and use that.
-Wow.
A NICE, CLEAN CUT
TA-DA
-My gosh.
-All right.
-He's showing what he has done.
-Looking prim.
He's really good at filleting.
He's making square shapes.
FINISHED PREPPING THE SHRIMP
PORK FAT, OYSTER SAUCE, GROUND PEPPER
AND FINISHING WITH
SOME SALT
-Adding salt.
-It didn't go in.
-I saw it too. It didn't go in.
-He didn't make it.
-Not even one grain.
-Nothing?
Nothing at all.
He can't throw it in anymore.
Did you see him do this?
-We got to see it live.
-Right?
What is he grinding?
-He's grinding shrimp meat.
-Shrimp meat.
He's grinding his life.
THE LID WON'T CLICK
…CAN'T SEE
-But he became farsighted.
-The lid isn't in place.
-And his grip is weak.
-He's grinding the shrimp.
Two minutes have gone by.
-Time flies.
-What now?
Time passes by too quickly.
GRABS AN ONION
CHOPPED INSTANTLY
-What's that? Shrimp?
-Shrimp.
I'm making tomato sauce right now,
but it's going to be spicy,
so it's called diavolo sauce.
-Diavolo.
1. COOK GARLIC, ONION IN OLIVE OIL
Are you boiling something?
She said she liked shrimp heads,
so I'll grind those too.
ADDING SHRIMP HEADS TO THE SAUCE
That's a touch for BIBI.
-He'll grind shrimp heads.
-Shrimp heads.
-Tomato sauce.
-It looks good.
CHILI FLAKES FOR SPICINESS
-He's opening the soju bottle.
-The red cap.
It's usually made with white wine,
but he's using soju instead.
What are those? Chili peppers?
Snacks.
-It's the spicy snacks.
-Spicy snacks.
RED FOR THE SISTERS
Hot snacks.
NICELY GROUND SHRIMP MEAT
He's topping cutlassfish pieces
with shrimp meat.
-On top?
-Whoa!
-Cutlassfish menbosha?
-I've never heard of it.
Shrimp and cutlassfish menbosha.
SC menbosha. It's a new attempt.
It'll have a nice texture and flavor.
After all, menbosha is a Chinese dish.
Would that not fall apart?
-It'll depend on the batter.
-Yes, he'll have to coat it.
How much water do I need, Eun-yeong?
Water? Stop.
Use your hands.
-Mix it with your hands.
-No more water.
-Why did you add more? That's too much!
-That's too much water.
Pour some out.
Keep stirring with your hands
until the batter gets thicker.
He has never made frying batter
in the Chinese way.
Is that okay?
-It's a bit thin.
-It looks fine.
-No, he'll cook it right away.
-Whatever. I'm done.
-What?
-It does look a bit thin.
-He put powder on it, so it's fine.
-Will it be okay?
But you have to cook menbosha
over low heat.
He can't stick to the original recipe.
He's not working with bread.
He's not using bread, so it's okay.
Four minutes have gone by.
NEW SEAFOOD: SCALLOP
INTO DIAVOLO PASTA SAUCE
GAS LIGHTER
Can you get my stove?
Sorry. Thank you.
-He had a moment to light his stove.
-How nice.
-How sweet.
-That's what Jong-won does.
PREPPED SCALLOPS INTO A PAN
Scallops.
Your favorite.
I really love scallops.
-Scallops?
-I love them.
2. COOK SCALLOPS IN OLIVE OIL,
THEN BASTE WITH BUTTER
Scallops become so delicious
when you cook them in a cast iron pan.
It comes out golden brown.
-They almost get stuck on the pan.
-Yes.
I'm making sauce for the fried shrimp
with coconut and meljeot.
-Meljeot?
-He's using anchovy jeotgal.
Meljeot, something the sisters love.
LOTS OF SEAFOOD EVERYWHERE
It's hard to imagine
what that dish will be like.
You won't be able to tell
if you're in Ulsan or Southeast Asia.
That's a new mix.
He's trying to create
an exotic taste from the sea.
His hands, son, move quickly.
That's why he's Son Jong-won.
He's peeling the shrimp.
I guess the 12-year difference
shows in their speed.
Jong-won makes his sauce.
HYUN-SUK MAKES HIS SAUCE TOO
He's crushing shrimp heads
and frying them in a pan.
BIBI said she liked them,
so he didn't throw them out.
Kelp seasoning.
Salted kelps.
-What's that?
-Mala xiang guo sauce.
SPLATTER
MALA SAUCE LAUNCHES
Oh, no!
-He's bleeding.
-Quiet.
Be quiet.
-What?
-He splattered it all over himself.
-What? On your uniform?
-On his uniform!
MALA XIANG GUO SAUCE
He wouldn't have done that before.
-No.
-But he's splattering himself.
He splashed the sauce on his uniform.
-He's getting older. Oh, no.
-He doesn't have enough power.
You should wear an apron
over your uniform.
He keeps it around his waist,
trying to look cool.
HIS LAST PIECE OF PRIDE
-I feel bad for him.
-He's getting old.
-Only eight minutes left?
-Whoa.
-You've used up seven minutes.
-Time is running out.
TAKES THE DIAVOLO SAUCE
Whoa. He's blending that.
PING!
EXPLODES
ANOTHER EMERGENCY SITUATION
EXPLODING WITH RED FLAVOR
AN EMERGENCY ALERT
Was the lid not on securely?
The blender explodes
when you blend something hot.
He was in a rush,
so he had no other choice.
-He's so calm. I'd make a huge fuss.
-He is.
But he didn't splash it on his uniform.
-It's only on the rag.
-Yes, he's still young.
He dodged it right away.
He pulled back instantly.
But Hyun-suk couldn't.
He just stood there and took it.
PULLING OUT THE PASTA
3. MIX PASTA WITH DIAVOLO SAUCE
AND MAKE CONCHIGLIE PASTA
What did he use for that?
-Shrimp heads, tomato, and pasta?
-Shrimp heads, tomato, and pasta.
HYUN-SUK USES SCALLOPS TOO
FEAT. MINCED GARLIC
GRABS THE MALA SOUP TOO
He's grinding the shrimp.
It's because BIBI likes the heads.
-It's BIBI's favorite.
-That's where all the flavor is.
Shrimp heads add so much umami.
You're right.
The sauce is ready for Hyun-suk.
That looks good.
-Glass noodles.
-Wide glass noodles.
It's strange to see Hyun-suk
making a Chinese dish.
-Five minutes, Jung-hwan!
-Okay.
Why is the time going by so quickly?
PREPPING WATER PARSLEY
Look how fast Chef Jong-won is.
He's so fast.
That was so cool.
He's really cool.
I think he looks really sexy
when he chops stuff.
How does he do that?
The glass noodles
look more like sea cucumbers.
DANG IT!
THIS TIME, THE SALT ALL GOES IN
AUTOMATIC RESPONSE
Should I add stalked sea squirt or not?
She said she liked them.
LOTS OF STALKED SEA SQUIRT THEN
He added stalked sea squirt.
DRAINING CUTLASSFISH SHRIMP FRITTERS
-Jung-hwan.
-Yes?
Do you see the conchiglie?
Can you try that?
-Let me try it.
-A dish for the Gyeongsang-do sisters.
-Does it taste like the sea?
-Like the sea.
Is Jong-won as real as ever?
-Son Jong-won.
-You're good.
-He's good!
WOW
-What does your father do?
-You got it going on.
Was your father a chef too?
What does your father do?
-That's not my father.
-You had your first hoe at six?
He fishes in Ulsan!
-Your father and I…
-What does he do?
…had hoe together!
Went to the sauna!
We did it all.
We had hoe together!
-We did everything together.
-Yes, man!
I pretty much brought you up.
ADDING SCALLOPS
INTO THE CONCH-SHAPED PASTA
-What's that?
-Starch.
What now?
It's for the texture.
-To thicken the sauce?
-To thicken it?
Did he have to use that?
-Chinese chefs don't do that.
-Yes, so why?
He's a fake.
That's Western style.
That's too Western.
-Chinese chefs just do it in a bowl.
-We just do it in a bowl.
That sauce Chef Hyun-suk just tasted.
-Chef Hyun-suk, our pillar.
-Our pillar!
Two minutes and five seconds.
So?
Is it worthy enough to win a star?
It is worthy enough for a star.
-He's going to win lots of stars.
-More than one or two?
It tastes both Western and Chinese.
-Really?
-At the same time?
It's mala, but kind of mild.
But it's still mala?
-That's so awesome.
-It still tastes Western.
-I'm sure.
-It's unique.
I have a feeling that you sisters
will have a tough time choosing.
-Really?
-Yes, it'll be tough.
4. MIX BUTTER WITH PARSLEY AND PARMESAN
He's mixing butter and parsley.
That's how you make escargot butter.
PARMESAN
ESCARGOT BUTTER
FIERY SNACK POWDER
PASTA GOES INTO THE OVEN
A minute and 40 seconds.
Didn't he say he'd fry the shrimp?
Didn't you say you'd fry shrimp?
-You have to do it quickly.
-Hurry up and do it.
It's an emergency.
-Shrimp.
-When will you fry the shrimp?
Whoa.
Hyun-suk, may I share your oil?
Okay. Sure.
ADDING SHRIMP TO HYUN-SUK'S OIL
My oil is overheated.
THIS ONE IS TOO COLD
TRYING IN HIS OIL
-That's too high.
-That's too hot.
-That pot is way too hot.
The dredge came off of the shrimp.
-Really?
-Yes, they're separated.
-No.
-It came apart?
He can't make the cocktail.
This is bad.
-It's an emergency.
-The rice paper came off.
-One minute left.
-Oh, no.
PUTTING ONE SHRIMP INTO HYUN-SUK'S POT
This one didn't come apart.
Do another one.
3. SERVE MALA JAPCHAE
AND FISH FRITTER WITH SHRIMP MALA SAUCE
Flying fish roe.
SPEED CHOPPING WATER PARSLEY
TOP THE DISH AND FINISH
-The cocktail.
-Chef Hyun-suk finishes!
Hyun-suk is done!
-Our pillar!
-He's done!
The cocktail.
STARTING THE COCKTAIL WITH 50 SECONDS LEFT
-Martini.
The cocktail.
RED CAP
WHITE CAP
One minute!
SEA SQUIRT
Sea squirt!
Forty. Thirty-nine.
ICE
PLEASE
-Shake it!
STRUCK WITH A DOPAMINE HIT
IN A FRENZY
FINISHED THE DRINK IN 15 SECONDS
ADDING STALKED SEA SQUIRT INTO THE GLASS
MEANWHILE, THE SHRIMPS ARE BEING NEGLECTED
GLANCES
Jong-won, these seem to be burning,
so let me get them.
JONG-WON'S STOVE: CAN'T BE SAVED
HYUN-SUK'S STOVE
Are the shrimps burnt?
No, one got burnt,
but I saved the other one.
SWEETLY PATRONIZING
BEGINS THE PRESENTATION
THE PASTA COMES OUT OF THE OVEN TOO
-Five.
-Four.
ON TOP OF THE PASTA
SITS A FRIED SHRIMP
DONE WITH THE COCKTAIL
-Chef Jong-won is done too.
-He's done.
JONG-WON FINISHES HIS DISHES
That was intense.
That was stressful.
THE INTENSE SEAFOOD ROUND IS NOW OVER
That could've gone so wrong at the end.
Now, both dishes are finished
for the Gyeongsang-do sisters.
SIGHS
My heart almost stopped in this round.
Right? He almost
couldn't make the cocktail.
I really wanted to try it,
-so it would've been…
-"What if we can't try it?"
-It took less than a minute.
-Please, the cocktail!
First, try Chef Hyun-suk's dish.
CHOI HYUN-SUK'S TAKE ON CHINESE CUISINE,
A SEAFOOD PARTY
CUTLASSFISH, SHRIMP, STALKED SEA SQUIRT,
SCALLOPS, AND FLYING FISH ROE
CHEF CHOI HYUN-SUK'S
LET'S GO CUTLASSFISH A STAR
TA-DA
It's piping hot.
SNIFF
Whoa.
-Earlier…
-It smells like shrimp innards.
Yes, it smells like seafood innards.
Toward the end,
he poured a huge batch of flying fish roe.
Let me take a picture. One second.
GASPING…
WAIT!
She's just like me.
I can't wait.
You two
seem rather aggressive when you see food.
THE SISTERS CHANGE IN FRONT OF FOOD
They're not listening.
They're not listening at all.
They don't care about the show.
IN PERFECT HARMONY
She's like the older sister sharing food
on her way to find refuge.
-She's forcing her to eat.
-In a war.
-"You have to eat this now!"
-"Eat while you can."
WERE YOU TWO AROUND BACK THEN?
SOLEMN
Cutlassfish fritters.
Does it smell like the sea?
Very much. It's such a pleasant smell.
EAT UP, GIRLS
It's Chef Hyun-suk's dish,
in Chinese-style.
He added shrimp heads, stalked sea squirt,
mala xiang guo sauce, and more.
NAKYOUNG TRIES
THE SEAFOOD FRITTER IN ONE BITE
Why do I feel like their parent?
It's so heartwarming.
It's literally rich.
The shrimp heads.
Mmm.
The richness of the shrimp heads.
-Does it taste strong?
-Very much.
He ground the shrimp heads.
BIBI TRIES THE FRITTER TOO
Is it still hot?
Just as Jung-hwan had mentioned,
it's not just one flavor.
-It's hard to explain.
-Yes, it's hard to explain.
Does it seem closer to Chinese cuisine?
-It does.
-If I had to choose one, yes.
If I had to choose.
-But the mala flavor isn't too strong.
-It's not?
The cutlassfish goes
really well with this.
-Shrimp?
-Yes.
They don't hurt each other.
The taste of shrimp heads is strong,
and cutlassfish tastes clean,
so it felt like shrimp heads
would overpower the other.
But the flavor is there.
I like the dredge too.
It's perfect.
It sat in the soup,
-so it became soft and chewy.
-Yes.
So this… Wow.
The moment you eat
a bite of boneless cutlassfish,
there's just something.
-Happiness, right?
-Also, he mixed
shrimp with pork fat, remember?
So that probably added a bouncy texture.
There's stalked sea squirt here too.
-You did?
-Yes.
She said she liked them, so he added some.
WILL IT GO WELL
WITH THE SHRIMP HEAD SAUCE?
It's made to their taste.
Stalked sea squirt.
You need it.
You need the stalked sea squirt.
It's so delicious.
Isn't it still hot?
It's not.
I think
they just can't feel heat and spiciness.
LAUGHING
Both heat and spiciness?
Excuse me. Are you two watching TV?
GUILTY
They're like siblings
watching TV and making comments.
"They eat so well."
CAN'T HEAR THEM
-But they're so small.
-Right?
IN A TRANCE
"It must be hot, but they can eat it."
That was steamy.
She's finishing everything.
-She must've been starving.
-Right?
Maybe all day long.
I haven't been to many restaurants,
but this tasted like a plate of luxury.
I've never had anything like this.
She's the poor female lead type.
STALKED SEA SQUIRT OVER FLOWERS
The rich guy's taste,
the poor girl's taste.
SHARING THE RICH TASTE
WITH THE POOR SISTERS
It hits me toward the end.
-The mala flavor.
Toward the end.
Was that intentional?
If I added more mala sauce
just because they liked it,
it would've killed
the briny flavor in the seafood.
-I see.
-Right.
So I added just a bit for the numbness
and tried to bring out
the seafood's flavor more.
I SEE!
Less for the food, more for his uniform.
It could've gone in there,
but I chose to put it here instead.
He sacrificed himself.
-That was his intention.
-He took the blow.
He couldn't let everything
go into the dish.
Next, Chef Jong-won's dish.
SPECIAL MELJEOT SAUCE AND ESCARGOT PASTA
ARE WE IN ULSAN OR FRANCE?
AND STALKED SEA SQUIRT?
CHEF SON JONG-WON'S
BIBI, NAKYOUNG, AS REAL AS EVER
May I come and shake
the cocktail?
Please shake them for a bit
next to the fridge owners.
SHAKE
-Let me shake it.
-He's shaking it.
SOJU MARTINI IN SEA SQUIRT GLASSES
There's stalked sea squirt inside.
-Thank you.
-How did he make this?
-He put stalked sea squirts on a skewer.
-He did.
-It's a martini.
-Martini.
It's usually made with olives.
It reminds me of stone sea pineapples
-you can eat by the sea.
-Sea pineapple shot.
It'll probably taste like that.
-So it reminds you of that.
-It'll feel like that.
-I see.
A toast.
BEING POLITE TO EACH OTHER?
OH, RIGHT!
They both love soju.
What's it like? Is it bad?
This is…
-What is this?
-"What is this?"
Yes, what is this?
A cocktail.
Well, yes.
-Does it taste weird?
-It doesn't.
Why does alcohol go so well
with sea squirt?
Right. But it doesn't
really taste like alcohol.
But it still tastes like alcohol.
And the smell of stalked sea squirt
suddenly hits you.
Yet it feels so good.
It tastes so pleasant.
But seriously, this is a huge wonder.
When you make martinis,
there are olives in it,
which are quite salty
making the drink smoother
while adding depth.
It's the same concept here.
After watching films like the 007 series,
I had always wanted to try martinis,
but when I ordered them,
they tasted awful to me.
-But this one is so good.
-It is?
I can just enjoy this.
She's already done.
Does it taste like the real deal?
I want more of this.
It was that good?
One more drink.
-Ask him for more.
-It was so good.
You can mix the red cap
with the white in two to one ratio.
-Red and white?
-So it's kind of strong.
It's high in proof.
-It's strong.
-Also, it's made with olive juice,
so instead of that,
I used the heart of palm juice.
I added a dash of lemon too,
trying to bring out
the cucumber-like flavor.
It's like magic.
-He's like a magician.
-I knew it.
Please try the dish now.
PASTA IN ESCARGOT SHAPE
Escargot.
POP!
NO WAY
-It really looks like escargot.
-It does.
Right away?
That pasta is shaped like a conch.
It's good.
THEIR HAPPY MUKBANG
"It's good."
I didn't know if I should serve
two shrimps or three,
but I thought I should serve just one.
What?
Then we can see BIBI eating the tail.
OH, THAT?
-That one.
-NaKyoung, leave me the tail.
HE PLANNED FOR THIS SIGHT TO UNFOLD?
It was intentional?
-It was intentional.
-NaKyoung eats the meat.
-That was it.
-What's it like?
Why is this sweet?
It tastes like sweet potato.
It tastes like sweet potato?
ONE SECOND
-As little meat as possible.
-Hey.
RIGHT!
SORRY! HAD SOME MEAT LEFT
Just the tail for BIBI.
-Isn't it sweet?
-Why?
-Is it?
-It really is sweet.
-Why is it sweet?
I had left it in alcohol for a bit.
-It tastes like sweet potato.
-It does, right?
-What's this?
-You can scoop some
-and put it on the pasta.
-It's for the pasta.
Jong-won has become quite brazen.
-Why?
-He burnt the other shrimp.
I see.
RUNNING AWAY
When Hyun-suk
took the shrimps out for him,
one was burnt and completely charred.
-He turned that into this?
-He spun a story.
You're funny these days.
"Share one with each other."
PASTA WITH MELJEOT SAUCE
What's it like?
"Who made this?"
Who made this?
-What is this?
-The sauce?
-Coconut.
-Right?
Did you use meljeot for this?
That and water parsley.
-Coconut. I can taste the coconut.
-Yes.
It tastes completely different
when I had it with the sauce
compared to when I had it by itself.
It's so good.
The umami of meljeot hits me first,
then it wraps up pleasantly
with the coconut flavor.
-It must taste clean.
-Yet it retained both flavors.
-Isn't it so good?
-That sauce.
-It must be good.
-It's so good.
So this sauce is different, right?
It's so good.
TWO LEFT
Scallops and shrimp.
-And pasta.
-I had nothing to eat today.
They eat so well.
The portion wasn't big,
so they share it.
Was the pasta good?
The conch-shaped pasta?
-It's so good.
-Is it?
Wait a second.
-Our viewers have nothing to eat.
-They got nothing.
-Oh, no.
-What?
-Nothing?
-It's time to decide.
-What? Nothing?
-Wait, there's nothing?
They'll decide.
Are these seats supposed to be miserable?
PICKING UP STUFF
Is this our punishment?
I have a bit left.
-There is some left.
-We'll let them try it.
Is there anything else?
She can't have shrimp.
-Do you not eat them?
-I'm allergic.
-Everything is made with shrimp.
-It's made with shrimp heads.
THE SHOCKING TRUTH
I'll take it.
Thank you.
What about Jong-won?
She can't eat them.
-But Nathan can eat some.
-He's fine.
-Really?
-Nathan's fine.
-Confiscated.
-Give it up.
-Why?
-It's for the guest.
That's mine!
TEARFUL
It's as if he's here alone.
First, Chef Hyun-suk's dish.
Can I at least smell it?
She won't let him eat it alone.
Aren't you allergic?
What's this thing that's popping?
-Flying fish roe.
-That adds a fun texture.
ALL CLEARED!
He eats so well.
WAILING
Teasing Patricia as much as he can.
TEASING HER ON ANOTHER LEVEL
AS ELEGANTLY AS POSSIBLE
YUM
Is it good?
Wait, this sauce.
WHAT IS THIS?
It's unique.
Yes, it's really unique.
Mmm.
-I love the bite too.
-The texture?
It reminds me of tteokbokki.
Yes, it's like tteokbokki,
-but with rosé sauce.
-Rosé tteokbokki.
IMMERSED
BOILING INSIDE
THE ELDEST ARE ON THE SAME FREQUENCY
He finishes every single bite.
ALL CLEARED!
Thank you. That was delicious.
It's now time to choose.
Press one for Jong-won
and two for Hyun-suk.
Make your decision
and press the button.
They both pressed the button.
I wonder how they voted.
Whoa!
Are they on the same page?
They're on the same page.
Two to zero.
Twice as humiliating.
-Exactly. How unfortunate.
-Yes.
The humiliation.
FEELING BAD
Which one became the winner?
-Let's find out the result.
-So?
Hyun-suk versus Jong-won.
Gyeongsang-do Sisters' Soul Food.
Jong-won, who's currently
the only one in first place.
But Hyun-suk had won
more rounds against him.
Who did BIBI and NaKyoung choose?
Who is it?
Who won the seafood round?
-The two good-looking chefs' round.
-Who's the winner?
Who is it?
SON JONG-WON WINS
It was Jong-won.
CHEF SON JONG-WON'S
BIBI, NAKYOUNG, AS REAL AS EVER WINS
Jong-won beats Hyun-suk
and takes the star.
It wasn't simply food.
It was a mix of cultures between
my hometown and something foreign
coming together within me,
which gives birth
to someone awesome like me.
AGREED
It was a new experience.
-I see.
-It was fun.
Jong-won, you now have 12 stars.
I wasn't paying attention to the oil,
and the temperature had risen too high.
-But Hyun-suk let me use his.
-That's true.
-That was how I could finish.
-And he got the shrimps out too.
I couldn't have done it without him.
It was for his little brother.
He sacrificed himself.
-And his outfit.
This is a huge loss.
I may have become torn apart,
tattered, and crumpled,
but I just wanted to see Jong-won do well
through my sacrifice.
ABOUT TO CRY
THAT WAS GOOD!
Were you a bit hesitant
when you got the shrimp out?
I didn't even hesitate for a second.
-I knew it.
-Whoa.
"Should I get this one out
and put it in the hotter oil?"
THE ELDEST IS ALSO THE FUNNIEST
Please put the star on him.
This is his 12th star.
He now has 12 wins in the sole 1st place.
He continues to widen the gap.
The hottest siblings
in the entertainment business.
You bought a car for Patricia?
NO WAY
TOTALLY SMUG
But the monthly payment is on me.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I didn't pay it off entirely.
I don't want to spoil her.
THE BROTHER'S THOUGHTFUL TAKE
I see some awful comments
asking if I'm Patricia
whenever I put on wigs.
His eyes are kind of glazed.
He always goes around looking like this.
Here are the orders.
The dishes to die for.
DISHES TO DIE FOR?
Are you trying to say goodbye to her?
One of us has to go.
FRIGHTENINGLY SWEET DISHES
FOR THE SIBLINGS
OUT FOR EACH OTHER'S NECK
A PILE OF SUGAR
-Whoa.
HERE TO SKYROCKET YOUR BLOOD SUGAR
Something smells sweet.
These are sweet dishes.
-Whoa.
-Look at Nathan.
HAVE THE SIBLINGS FAINTED?
STRUCK BY THE BLOOD SUGAR SPIKE
NEXT UP, SPICINESS!
FULL OF CHEONGYANG PEPPERS
THROWING IN EXTREMELY SPICY THINGS
BLECH!
THE SPICIEST DISH YET?
It's extremely spicy!
You'd die.
I'm not dead.
THE TWO WITH A HIGH SPICE TOLERANCE
-This isn't spicy?
-Is something wrong with me?
-I was surprised.
-It's so good.
WHICH DISH DID THE SIBLINGS FALL FOR?
-It's insane.
-It's so good, though.
Can you two get closer?
Closer.
-Are we getting paid extra for this?
-I was going to ask.
Subtitle translation by:
Eunsook Youn